<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss version="0.91">
<channel>
	<title>Drugs.com - Daily MedNews</title>
	<link>https://www.drugs.com/medical-news.html</link>
	<description>Headline news from Drugs.com. Comprehensive and up-to-date drug news for both consumers and healthcare professionals.</description>
	<language>en</language>

	<item>
		<title>Make Learning Fun, and Kids Learn More</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/make-learning-fun-kids-learn-more-85296.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Make+Learning+Fun%2C+and+Kids+Learn+More</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- Make it fun, and they will learn.
That&apos;s the conclusion of a new Canadian study that analyzed a kindergarten teaching program that favors playful activities and socializing over sit-down lectures. In the end, the...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 14:09:55 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>FDA OKs New Pill for Type 2 Diabetes, Rybelsus (Semaglutide)</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/fda-oks-new-pill-type-2-diabetes-rybelsus-semaglutide-85295.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=FDA+OKs+New+Pill+for+Type+2+Diabetes%2C+Rybelsus+%28Semaglutide%29</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- A new pill to lower blood sugar for people with type 2 diabetes was approved by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration on Friday.
The drug, Rybelsus (semaglutide) is the first pill in a class of drugs called glucagon-like...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 14:09:17 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Anemia During Pregnancy Tied to Higher Odds for Autism, ADHD in Kids</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/anemia-during-pregnancy-tied-higher-odds-autism-adhd-kids-85283.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Anemia+During+Pregnancy+Tied+to+Higher+Odds+for+Autism%2C+ADHD+in+Kids</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- Women who suffer from anemia early in pregnancy are at risk for having a child with autism, attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) and intellectual disabilities, a study by Swedish researchers suggests.
The study...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 12:09:52 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Flavored E-Cigarettes May Make Asthma Worse</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/flavored-e-cigarettes-may-make-asthma-worse-85282.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Flavored+E-Cigarettes+May+Make+Asthma+Worse</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- Black licorice, banana pudding and other flavored electronic cigarette liquids may make respiratory diseases like asthma worse, a new international study finds.
Vaping has surged in recent years, especially among young...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 12:09:26 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>AHA News: Adopted Baby&apos;s Unexpected Heart Problem Brought Unexpected Joy</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/aha-news-adopted-baby-s-unexpected-heart-problem-brought-unexpected-joy-85284.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=AHA+News%3A+Adopted+Baby%27s+Unexpected+Heart+Problem+Brought+Unexpected+Joy</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 (American Heart Association News) -- When their hopes of adopting a child from China were stretched thin by years of wait, Vanessa and Chris Zoog asked for a baby with a physical issue &amp;ndash; one who could use an extra dollop...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 12:09:22 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Low Vitamin D Levels, Shorter Life?</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/low-vitamin-d-levels-shorter-85281.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Low+Vitamin+D+Levels%2C+Shorter+Life%3F</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- Young and middle-aged adults with low vitamin D levels may live shorter lives, a large study suggests.
The findings come from a 20-year follow-up of more than 78,000 Austrian adults. Researchers found that those with low...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 12:09:13 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Sick Americans Turning to Medical Pot for Help</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/sick-americans-turning-medical-pot-help-85280.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Sick+Americans+Turning+to+Medical+Pot+for+Help</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- More Americans use marijuana to help them cope with an illness than just to get high, a new study finds.
Nearly 46% of those who use pot say they do so because of a medical condition, compared with 22% who say they use...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 12:09:01 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Smarter Snacks for Football Fans</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/smarter-snacks-football-fans-85277.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Smarter+Snacks+for+Football+Fans</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- This year, when the gang comes over to watch football, score big with these healthy treats.
Rich and creamy onion dip with chips is a favorite and so easy to make by mixing sour cream into a flavor packet. But most dip...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 09:09:27 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Don&apos;t Let Fear of Cancer Keep You From Doctor Visits</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/don-t-let-fear-cancer-keep-you-doctor-visits-85276.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Don%27t+Let+Fear+of+Cancer+Keep+You+From+Doctor+Visits</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- As terrified as you might be of a possible cancer diagnosis from your doctor, a new study warns that you still need to keep your appointment.
Why? Patients who blow off appointments for cancer symptoms are 12% more likely...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 09:09:20 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Take a Fresh Look at Fitness Classes</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/fresh-look-fitness-classes-85278.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Take+a+Fresh+Look+at+Fitness+Classes</link>
		<description>FRIDAY, Sept. 20, 2019 -- Tired of taking the same old cardio class? It&apos;s time to explore some of the combination classes being offered at both large gyms and small, more personalized fitness centers.
One of the most popular options is the...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 09:09:20 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Health Highlights: Sept. 20, 2019</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/health-highlights-sept-20-2019-85279.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Health+Highlights%3A+Sept.+20%2C+2019</link>
		<description>Here are some of the latest health and medical news developments, compiled by the editors of HealthDay:
Vaping-Linked Lung Illness Claims 8th Life
A Missouri man in his 40s is the eighth person in the U.S. to die from complications of a lung...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 08:09:31 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Health Tip: Controllable Stroke Risk Factors</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/health-tip-controllable-stroke-risk-factors-85275.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Health+Tip%3A+Controllable+Stroke+Risk+Factors</link>
		<description>-- More than 750,000 people have a stroke each year in the United States, says Cleveland Clinic. But as many as half of all strokes are preventable, the clinic says.
Risk factors that are under all or partial control include:

High blood...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 07:09:57 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Health Tip: Hurricane Readiness</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/health-tip-hurricane-readiness-85274.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Health+Tip%3A+Hurricane+Readiness</link>
		<description>-- An important part of hurricane readiness is collecting supplies that will help keep your family safe, says the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
Before a hurricane, the CDC suggests that you:

Prepare an emergency water...</description>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 07:09:31 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Hysterectomy Procedure Tied to Worse Cancer Outcomes</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/hysterectomy-procedure-tied-worse-cancer-outcomes-85268.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Hysterectomy+Procedure+Tied+to+Worse+Cancer+Outcomes</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- Women who must have their uterus removed should be wary of a procedure called uncontained uterine power morcellation, Yale University researchers warn.
This once common surgical option for hysterectomy or myomectomy...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 16:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Opioid Prescriptions for Eye Surgery Patients Surge</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/opioid-prescriptions-eye-surgery-patients-surge-85267.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Opioid+Prescriptions+for+Eye+Surgery+Patients+Surge</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- Though eye surgery has gotten easier for patients, the percentage who filled an opioid prescription after an eye operation tripled between 2000 and 2014, a new study reports.
&quot;This really is surprising, given that there...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 14:09:57 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Cases of Vaping-Linked Lung Illness Rise to 530 Across 38 States: CDC</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/cases-vaping-linked-lung-illness-rise-530-across-38-states-cdc-85264.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Cases+of+Vaping-Linked+Lung+Illness+Rise+to+530+Across+38+States%3A+CDC</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- The number of confirmed or suspected severe lung illnesses linked to vaping has leapt to 530 cases across 38 states and the Virgin Islands, U.S. health officials reported Thursday.
There have also been seven confirmed...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 14:09:55 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Keeping Blood Sugar Steady Helps You Live Longer With Diabetes</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/keeping-blood-sugar-steady-helps-you-live-longer-diabetes-85265.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Keeping+Blood+Sugar+Steady+Helps+You+Live+Longer+With+Diabetes</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- If you have type 2 diabetes, keeping your blood sugar levels stable over time may be key to living longer.
New research finds that people who have more swings in their blood sugar levels were more than twice as likely to...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 14:09:50 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Flavored E-Cigarette Use Soars Among Young Adults</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/flavored-e-cigarette-soars-among-young-adults-85266.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Flavored+E-Cigarette+Use+Soars+Among+Young+Adults</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- New research suggests that the e-cigarette industry&apos;s marketing efforts have latched onto a new age group.
Flavored e-cigarettes have now grown wildly popular among young adults aged 18 to 24 who don&apos;t smoke tobacco, the...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 14:09:01 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Scientists Discover New Way Fat Harms Your Arteries</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/scientists-discover-new-way-fat-harms-your-arteries-85251.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Scientists+Discover+New+Way+Fat+Harms+Your+Arteries</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- Scientists may have found a way that obesity directly damages the arteries and contributes to heart disease -- a discovery that they say could eventually lead to new treatments.
The British researchers found that in...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 12:09:57 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Just 2 Weeks on the Couch Starts to Damage Your Body</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/just-2-weeks-couch-starts-damage-your-body-85250.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Just+2+Weeks+on+the+Couch+Starts+to+Damage+Your+Body</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- A new study proves that the old adage &quot;use it or lose it&quot; is definitely true when it comes to fitness.
After just two weeks of sedentary behavior, formerly fit people had:

A decline in heart and lung health
Increased...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 12:09:53 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>For People at High Risk, Evidence That Exercise Might Slow Alzheimer&apos;s</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/risk-evidence-exercise-might-slow-alzheimer-s-85252.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=For+People+at+High+Risk%2C+Evidence+That+Exercise+Might+Slow+Alzheimer%27s</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- For people at risk of Alzheimer&apos;s disease, working out a couple of times a week might at least slow the onset of the illness, new research suggests.
Regular exercise over a year slowed the degeneration of the part of the...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 12:09:31 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>AHA News: These Diets Helped Women With Diabetes Cut Heart Attack, Stroke Risk</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/aha-news-these-diets-helped-women-diabetes-cut-heart-attack-stroke-risk-85253.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=AHA+News%3A+These+Diets+Helped+Women+With+Diabetes+Cut+Heart+Attack%2C+Stroke+Risk</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 (American Heart Association News) -- Eating patterns similar to the Mediterranean diet and the blood pressure-lowering DASH may help older women with Type 2 diabetes ward off heart attacks, strokes and related problems, new...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 12:09:23 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Parents, Throw the Garden at Your Picky Eater</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/parents-throw-garden-your-picky-eater-85246.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Parents%2C+Throw+the+Garden+at+Your+Picky+Eater</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- When it comes to convincing your kids that vegetables taste good, variety might be the key to success.
New research suggests that offering children more than one type of vegetable may improve the chances that they&apos;ll eat...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 09:09:54 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Maker Halts Distribution of Generic Zantac Due to Possible Carcinogen</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/maker-halts-distribution-zantac-due-possible-carcinogen-85245.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Maker+Halts+Distribution+of+Generic+Zantac+Due+to+Possible+Carcinogen</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- Novartis, the maker of a generic form of the popular heartburn drug Zantac, said Wednesday it will cease distribution of the medicine after investigations suggested that generic and branded versions contain a known...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 09:09:35 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Can You Still Be Healthy If You&apos;re Overweight?</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/can-you-still-healthy-if-you-re-overweight-85247.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Can+You+Still+Be+Healthy+If+You%27re+Overweight%3F</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- If you&apos;re overweight but have dodged chronic health issues like high cholesterol and high blood pressure, you might not think that losing weight is a priority. But an analysis of five years of records on 3.5 million...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 09:09:16 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Foods That Will Make You Feel Full Faster</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/foods-make-you-feel-full-faster-85248.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Foods+That+Will+Make+You+Feel+Full+Faster</link>
		<description>THURSDAY, Sept. 19, 2019 -- When you get the urge for a snack, you might not think that a slice of turkey can have the same lip-smacking effect as a handful of chips. But scientists have known for some time that protein is the most efficient...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 09:09:08 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Health Highlights: Sept. 19, 2019</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/health-highlights-sept-19-2019-85249.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Health+Highlights%3A+Sept.+19%2C+2019</link>
		<description>Here are some of the latest health and medical news developments, compiled by the editors of HealthDay:
More U.S. Teens Vaping Nicotine
Among high school seniors across America about 25% are vaping nicotine e-cigarettes this year, a jump from 21%...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 08:09:42 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Health Tip: Managing Reactive Hypoglycemia</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/health-tip-managing-reactive-hypoglycemia-85244.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Health+Tip%3A+Managing+Reactive+Hypoglycemia</link>
		<description>-- Reactive hypoglycemia refers to low blood sugar after a meal, says Mayo Clinic. The condition has a variety of causes, from drinking alcohol to metabolic disorders.
People with reactive hypoglycemia may have symptoms including weakness,...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 07:09:26 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Health Tip: Gaining Weight</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/health-tip-gaining-weight-85243.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Health+Tip%3A+Gaining+Weight</link>
		<description>-- Being underweight may be associated with health problems such as anemia and fertility issues, says the American Academy of Family Physicians.
The academy mentions healthier ways to gain weight:

Add healthier calories to your diet by eating...</description>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 07:09:09 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>All-in-One Pill Helps Protect Heart</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/all-one-pill-helps-protect-heart-85236.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=All-in-One+Pill+Helps+Protect+Heart</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- Could popping just one pill a day keep your heart and blood vessels humming along for years to come?
Possibly. Researchers just tested a combo pill containing low doses of two blood pressure medications, a statin and a...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 17:09:46 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Intense Gaming Can Trigger Irregular Heartbeat, Fainting in Some Players</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/intense-gaming-can-trigger-irregular-heartbeat-fainting-some-players-85237.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Intense+Gaming+Can+Trigger+Irregular+Heartbeat%2C+Fainting+in+Some+Players</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- Video games that guarantee heart-stopping action might come dangerously close to fulfilling that promise in some players.
A handful of video gamers have passed out when intense sessions caused their heartbeat to lapse...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 17:09:07 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Tiny Genetic Tweak May Stop Ebola Virus in Its Tracks</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/tiny-genetic-tweak-may-stop-ebola-virus-tracks-85235.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Tiny+Genetic+Tweak+May+Stop+Ebola+Virus+in+Its+Tracks</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- New experiments in monkeys suggest that one slight alteration to the DNA of the Ebola virus might render it harmless to humans.
Changing just a single protein appears to activate the body&apos;s immune system to fight off...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 16:09:27 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>C-Section Delivery Might Alter Newborn&apos;s &apos;Microbiome&apos;</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/c-section-delivery-might-alter-newborn-s-microbiome-85233.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=C-Section+Delivery+Might+Alter+Newborn%27s+%27Microbiome%27</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- New research reveals that the bacterial composition of a newborn&apos;s gut may be dependent on how the baby is delivered.
Gut bacteria found in children delivered by cesarean section largely reflected the bacterial...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 14:09:45 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>New Healthy Drinks Guidelines for Kids: Skip the Soy, Avoid Sugars</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/new-healthy-drinks-guidelines-kids-skip-soy-avoid-sugars-85232.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=New+Healthy+Drinks+Guidelines+for+Kids%3A+Skip+the+Soy%2C+Avoid+Sugars</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- Four of America&apos;s biggest health organizations are banding together to urge parents to better monitor the drinks their young kids sip each day.
The take-home message from the new &quot;Healthy Drinks, Healthy Kids&quot;...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 14:09:21 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Chemicals From Heat-Not-Burn Tobacco Devices Not Harmless: Study</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/chemicals-heat-not-burn-tobacco-devices-not-harmless-study-85234.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Chemicals+From+Heat-Not-Burn+Tobacco+Devices+Not+Harmless%3A+Study</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- Chemical emissions from heat-not-burn tobacco devices are lower than from conventional cigarettes, but they&apos;re still high enough to be cause for concern, researchers report.
The makers of such devices claim that they...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 14:09:12 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Opioid Epidemic Tied to Doubling of Dangerous Heart Infections</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/opioid-epidemic-tied-doubling-dangerous-heart-infections-85221.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Opioid+Epidemic+Tied+to+Doubling+of+Dangerous+Heart+Infections</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- Addiction and overdose deaths aren&apos;t the only consequence of America&apos;s opioid epidemic. Cases of a potentially deadly heart infection have risen alarmingly, too, a new study finds.
This bacterial infection, called...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 12:09:34 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Age Often Dampens Narcissists&apos; Self-Love, Study Finds</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/age-often-dampens-narcissists-self-love-study-finds-85218.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Age+Often+Dampens+Narcissists%27+Self-Love%2C+Study+Finds</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- Narcissism is not a good look at any age, but new research suggests it fades as people enter their 40s.
However, the degree of decline in narcissism varies between individuals and can be related to their career and...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 09:09:59 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Staying Healthy Now to Work Into Older Age</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/staying-healthy-now-work-into-older-age-85220.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Staying+Healthy+Now+to+Work+Into+Older+Age</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- While you can take Social Security benefits at age 62 and get 75% of your maximum, waiting until you reach full retirement age (between age 66 and 67 depending on the year you were born) gets you much closer to the full...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 09:09:48 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Stock up on These Fall Superfoods</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/stock-up-these-fall-superfoods-85219.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Stock+up+on+These+Fall+Superfoods</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- Butternut squash, Brussels sprouts and apples are all amazing fall superfoods and the perfect reason to get cooking.
Cheap and versatile, butternut squash is loaded with fiber and vitamin A. For an easy butternut squash...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 09:09:43 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>Four-Legged Friends Help Buffer Loss of a Spouse</title>
		<link>https://www.drugs.com/news/four-legged-friends-help-buffer-loss-spouse-85217.html?utm_source=ddc&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=Four-Legged+Friends+Help+Buffer+Loss+of+a+Spouse</link>
		<description>WEDNESDAY, Sept. 18, 2019 -- The loss of a loved one is one of life&apos;s most stressful events. But new research suggests that having a furry loved one still at home may help ease the pain.
Investigators looked at 437 older adults, some of whom lost a...</description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 09:09:30 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>